A Guide to the American Lung Association of Virginia (ALAV) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- PEDIATRIC LUNG DISEASE COMMITTEE BY F. STANFORD MASSIE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ALL MEMBERS OF VLA PEDIATRIC LUNG DISEASE, ET AL., 1978-1979, 9-D, 2-N, 11-TLS, 5-TL (Box-folder 150:005)
- PEDIATRIC LUNG DISEASE BY FINDLEY RAYMOND, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: SELECTED CLASS MEMBERS, ET AL., 1975-1976, 1-N, 1-D (Box-folder 150:006)
- PEMBINE CONFERENCE, BLUE RIDGE SANATORIUM PATIENT FILES, 1953, 11-D, 11-TLS, 14-TL (Box-folder 150:007)
- BADGES, -1949, 1-D, 1-medal (Box-folder 150:008)
  INCLUDES A 1920 BADGE/MEDAL FROM NTA 22ND MEETING
- PERFORMANCE INDEX FOLLOW-UP COMMITTEE BY LOUISE CAMPBELL, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: E.F. HUGHES, ET AL., 1966-1968, 2-TL, 10-D, 2-N (Box-folder 150:009)
- PERFORMANCE INDEX COMMITTEE BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: J. YORK WELBORN, ET AL., 1966-1967, 7-TL, 8-D, 2-TLS, 1-W, 1-ALS (Box-folder 150:010)
- PERFORMANCE BY EUGENE HUGHES, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MEMBERS OF PERFORMANCE INDEX COMMITTEE, ET AL., 1965-1966, 3-N, 1-TL, 3-TLS, 12-D, 1-DS (Box-folder 150:011)
- PERFORMANCE INDEX COMMITTEE, 1965-1966, 1-N, 25-D (Box-folder 150:012)
- PERFORMANCE INDEX COMMITTEE, 1965-1966, 10-D, 1-ANS, 2-TLS, 10-N, 2-TL (Box-folder 151:001)
- PERFORMANCE INDEX COMMITTEE MINUTES BY VTRDA, 1965-1966, 2-D (Box-folder 151:002)
- PERFORMANCE COMMITTEE INDEX, SUB-COMMITTEE ON ADMINISTRATION BY E.C. DRASH, W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MEMBERS OF SUB-COMMITTEE, ET AL., 1965-1966, 1-N, 6-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 151:003)
- PERFORMANC INDEX COMMITTEE, SUB-COMMITTEE ON FUND-RAISING BY VTRDA, 1965-1966, 7-D, 1-N, 2-TL (Box-folder 151:004)
- PERFORMANCE INDEX COMMITTEE, SUB-COMMITTEE ON PROGRAMS BY VTRDA, 1965-1966, 6-D, 1-TL, 1-N (Box-folder 151:005)
- PERFORMANCE INDEX FOLLOW-UP COMMITTEE, 1968-1969, 3-D (Box-folder 151:006)
- PERFORMANCE REVIEW COMMITTEE, VLA BY VLA, ET AL., 1978-1979, 38-D, 5-N, 2-map, 2-TL, 4-AN, 1-TLS (Box-folder 151:007)
- PERSONNEL COMMITTEE BY TAYLOR COPPING, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ROY DAVIS, ET AL., 1980-1981, 15-D, 1-TLS, 2-TL (Box-folder 151:008)
- PERSONNEL COMMITTEE BY TAYLOR COPPNG, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: P.R. CLARKE, ET AL., 1976-1980, 13-D, 4-N, 7-TL (Box-folder 151:009)
- PERSONNEL AND OFFICE ADMINISTRATION COMMITTEE, 1968-1975, 19-D, 2-N, 10-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 151:010)
- PERSONNEL AND OFFICE ADMINISTRATION COMMITTEE, 1963-1968, 7-TL, 1-TLS, 9-N (Box-folder 151:011)
- PERSONNEL AND OFFICE ADMINISTRATION COMMITTEE, 1962-1963, 16-D (Box-folder 151:012)
- PERSONNEL AND OFFICE ADMINISTRATION COMMITTEE BY VTA, 1961-1962, 8-D, 2-N, 2-TL (Box-folder 152:001)
- PERSONNEL AND OFFICE ADMINISTRATION COMMITTEE BY WIRT COLEMEN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: D.H. ALLEY, ET AL., 1957-1961, 31-D, 2-TLS, 5-TL, 3-N (Box-folder 152:002)
- PERSONNEL AND ADMINISTRATIVE AUDIT-VTA BY VTA, 1960, 2-D (Box-folder 152:003)
- PERSONNEL COMMITTEE BY VTA, 1955-1957, 15-D, 3-TL (Box-folder 152:004)
- PERSONNEL COMMITTEE BY MR. BARRIE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MEMBERS, ET AL., 1952-1955, 25-D, 10-TL, 1-AL, 7-N (Box-folder 152:005)
- PERSONNEL COMMITTEE--CORRESPONDENCE BY VTA, 1951-1952, 2-D, 3-N, 4-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 152:006)
- PERSONNEL PERFORMANCE EVALUATION--CLERICAL BY GEORGE WILLIAMS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1956, 1-TLS, 1-N (Box-folder 152:007)
- PERSONNEL PRACTICES BY VTA, N.D., 1-AD, 17-D (Box-folder 152:008)
- PERSONNEL BY ILLINOIS TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATION, VTA, ET AL., 1951-1952, 1-N, 7-D (Box-folder 152:009)
- PERSONNEL--VTA BY VTA, 1950, 3-AN, 6-AD, 24-TLS, 13-D, 29-TL, 4-ALS, 1-N (Box-folder 152:010)
- PERSONNEL--VTA, 1940-1949, 31-D, 8-ALS, 38-TLS, 53-TL, 10-N, 4-NEWSCLIPS, 1-AN (Box-folder 152:011)
- PERSONNEL--VTA, 1940-1949, 17-D, 49-TL, 34-TLS, 9-AN, 5-NEWSCLIPS,9-PHOTOS,32-ALS (Box-folder 152:012)
- PERSONNEL--VTA BY EXECUTIVE SECRETARY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: GLADYS ALLISON, ET AL., 1930-1939, 44-TL,44-ALS,4-AN,3-NEWSCLIP,10-TLS,3-D,1-PHOTO,2-N (Box-folder 153:001)
- PERSONNEL, 1930-1939, 8-AN,1-AD,13-TLS,20-TL,27-ALS,2-NEWSCLIP,2-N,1-D (Box-folder 153:002)
- PERSONNEL--VTA BY BERTHA HORMER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MARY GAMMON, ET AL., 1920-1929, 38-ALS, 5-TLS, 6-AN, 2-NEWSCLIPS, 12-TL, 2-D (Box-folder 153:003)
- PERSONNEL-VTA BY ASSISTANT SECRETARY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: NORA REYNOLDS, ET AL., 1920-1929, 25-TL, 6-TLS, 41-ALS, 1-D, 4-AN (Box-folder 153:004)
- PERSONNEL-VTA BY PHILIP JACOBS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: AGNES RANDOLPH, ET AL., -1920, 15-AN, 19-TL, 22-ALS,10-TLS,2-NEWSCLIP,11-D,6-N,1-DS (Box-folder 153:005)
- PERSONNEL--VIRGINIA AYLOR, MRS. E.P. BABCOCK, TB ASSOCIATION SERVING DINWIDDIE, MRS. W.I. BARBER BY LOUISE CLARY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ROBERT BARRIE, ET AL., N.D., 5-D,1-AN,3-TLS,1-ALS,2-TL (Box-folder 153:006)
- PERSONNEL--MRS. J. REGINALD BAILEY BY LILLIAN EISENHART, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: STEVE BAILEY, ET AL., N.D., 4-TL,13-D,1-NS,8-N,26-DS,1-AN,1-ALS,1-TLS,1-c. (Box-folder 153:007)
- PERSONNEL--ROBERT BARRIE BY ROBERT BARRIE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: EMMET C. MATHEWS, ET AL., 1951, 36-D,4-N,3-D,2-c.d.,17-TLS,1-NEWSCLIP,1-D.S.,1-PHOTO (Box-folder 153:008)
- PERSONNEL--RICHARD BARNES BY THOMAS MOAK, JR., ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CHARLES E. JOHNS, ET AL., N.D., 6-TL, 2-TLS, 12-N, 1-DS, 3-D (Box-folder 154:001)
- PERSONNEL--MRS. DAVID BELL, MRS. PEARL BINGHAM, BRENDA BIRD, ELIZABETH BOKEL, FRED BROECKER, MRS. FRED BROECKER, ELEANOR BROWN, RICHARD EUGENE BUNCH, MRS. ABNER KEEN BUTTERWORTH, MARGARET RUTH CAMPBELL, JAMES CARR BY ROBERT BARRIE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: RAYMOND HOGAN, ET AL., N.D., 14-D,3-ALS,16-TL,9-TLS,2-AN,2-NEWSCLIP,18-N,1-DS (Box-folder 154:002)
- PERSONNEL--EDGAR CARROL BY EDGAR CARROL, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., N.D., 2-AN,2-ALS,9-D,1-NS,10-TL,13-DS,2-c.d.,5-TLS,8-N,2-NEWS (Box-folder 154:003)
- PERSONNEL--GWENDOLYN MURRAY CARSTARPHEN, MRS. NATHALIE ELSA CASSELL, MRS. VAN CHICHESTER, CHARLOTTE CLARK, MARIAN CLEMENTS, KATHLEEN COATES, MRS. ROBERTS COLLEY, MRS. ROBERT LEE CONSOLVO, ELIZABETH COLLIER COX, MARGARET COVILLE, ET AL. BY GWEN CARSTARPHEN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., N.D., 1-AN,21-D,7-DS,10-TLS,1-ADS,1-c.d,2-NS,10-TL,4-N (Box-folder 154:004)
  LOUIS FARRELL CRANE, MARGARET CROCKET, MRS. RUSSELL CUMMINGS
- PERSONNEL--ERIN DAVIS, LIEUNTENANT RONNIE DAVIS, LOIS DECK, HILDA DELUCIA, BLANCHE DIBBLE, BARBARA DISHNER, ERROL DONAHUE, LURLINE DRAKE, HENRY DUCKMAN, TRINIDAD FRANCIS DUMLAO, JR. BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ERIN DAVIS, ET AL., N.D., 3-AD,6-N,1-ALS,13-TL,14-TLS,7-DS,10-D,1-ANS (Box-folder 154:005)
- PERSONNEL--EARL DUNKLEE BY W.W. WENDT, E AL./ADDRESSED TO: M.L. SLAVIN, ET AL., N.D., 13-D,2-AN,22-TL,20-TLS,32-N,6-DS,2-NEWSCLIP,3-NS,1-ALS (Box-folder 154:006)
- PERSONNEL--SUZANNE DURLING, CHRISTINE JOLLY EASTHAM, HARRY JAMES EDWARDS, JR., ROBERT ELLYSON, T.L. ELMORE, MRS. ROBERT ETTER, AGNES EVANS, LUCY FINNEGAN, MRS. D.D. FORREST, SAMUEL FORREST BY SUSANNE DURLING, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., N.D., 2-NEWS,1-AN,2-ANS,5-ALS,6-N,13-D,10-DS,2-NS,21-TL (Box-folder 154:007)
  14-TLS
- PERSONNEL--LESLIE FOSTER, N.D., 7-D,2-NEWS,1-ALS,10-TL,12-TLS,2-DS,2-N (Box-folder 154:008)
- PERSONNEL--WESLEY FRANKLIN, JR., EDWIN GAHAN, KATHRYN GAHAN, FRANCES GALLAGHER, LANNIE GARDNER, MRS. ZENITH LOUISE GRANT, MARGARET HALE, SAMUEL HENRY GUZE III, WANDA LEE HALE, WILLIAM HALES, AUBREY HALL, JR., MRS. GLADY HALL, MARY JANE HAMILTON BY WESLEY FRANKLIN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WEDNT, ET AL., N.D., 29-TLS,23-D,25-TL,1-ANS,7-N,8-DS,1-AN,1-NEWS,1-c.d.s. (Box-folder 154:009)
  NORA SPENCER HAMNER, EDWARD HANNON, JR., MRS. J.L. HARDY
- PERSONNEL--JOHN HANSBARGER BY LOUISE EAGLEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: RUTH POLEY, ET AL., N.D., 11-N,6-DS,4-ALS,16-TLS,37-TL, 13-D (Box-folder 154:010)
- PERSONNEL--RUTH HARRIS, GLADYS LEWIS HARRIS BY GERALD ENGLISH, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: RUTH HARRIS, ET AL., N.D., 9-TL,9-N,1-AN,10-DS,9-D,7-TLS, 2-ALS (Box-folder 155:001)
- PERSONNEL--RUTH WEEKS HARVEY, MATHEW HAWLEY, KATHRYN HAYMES, ROBERT HELTON BY LAWRENCE CRUMBLISS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: JERRY NORVILLE, ET AL., N.D., 2-ALS,13-D,13-TL,12-TLS,12-TLS,7-N,1-NS,2-DS,2-c.d.s (Box-folder 155:002)
- PERSONNEL--BENJAMIN HICKS, PATTI HIGGINBOTHAM, JOYCE HILLDRUP, JAMES HUNT, MRS. WILLIAM JOHNSON, CARL JONES, LUCY JONES, GRACE KELLY, LUCILLE KESTING, MRS. ERNEST KITTS, ELLEN LAING, CHARLES LAMPMAN, GORIA LANE BY BENJAMIN HICKS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LINDSAY SCOTT, ET AL., N.D., 15-TL, 8-TLS,16-D,1-N,10-DS,1-AN (Box-folder 155:003)
- PERSONNEL--JEANNE LEWIS, CHARLES LINEBACK, O.H. LINCK, VIRGINIA LINDAMOOD, SIMUEL LOGAN, HELEN LUMPKIN BY JEANNE LEWIS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., N.D., 6-TLS,8-D,10-TL,1-photo,5-DS,1-AD,1-ANS,5-N,1-NEWS (Box-folder 155:004)
- PERSONNEL--NANCY LUTZ BY RUTH POLEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: SAMUEL SNEED ET AL., N.D., 19-TL,3-TLS,3-ALS,14-DS,10-N,1-ANS,8-D (Box-folder 155:005)
- PERSONNEL-HAROLD MCGEE BY W.W WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: HAROLD MCGEE, ET AL., 1945, 10-D,9-TL,3-DS,1-AN,17-N,6-TLS (Box-folder 155:006)
- PERSONNEL--GWEN MCWORTER, MRS. GEORGE MARSHALL, MRS. WAYNE MARTIN, RONALD MARION, HARRIET MATTOX, MARY MAXEY, MRS. J.E. MAY, LOUISE MCCONNELL, VALERIE MCCOY, CURTIS MCMILLAN, MRS. MARION MOAK, MRS. CHARLES MONCURE BY GRAYDON DORSCH, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ROBERT BARRIE, ET AL., N.D., 15-TLS,4-N,14-TL,1-AN,23-D-1-ALS,8-DS,1-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 155:007)
- MYRTLE MOORE, MARY MORGAN, ANNA MORRIS, DANNY MORRIS, FLORENCE MORRISON, MRS. P.G. MORRISETTE, MRS. P.M. MORTON, DON MUMPOWER, MRS. I.N. (JEAN) MUNSEY, MRS. BASIL MURRAY BY WALLACE HOOK ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., N.D., 15-D,9-TL,8-TLS,8-DS,5-N,2-c.d.s, 2-AN (Box-folder 155:008)
- PERSONNEL--MAX MURRAY, MRS. R.A. NAPIER, MARIE PARKER, RUTH PARKER, WILLIAM PARKER, FRANK PERKINS, DONALD PERRY, HARVEY PHILLIPS, DOROTHY PIRICZKY, ELEANOR POMFREY BY MAX MURRAY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., N.D., 8-D,7-TLS,18-TL,11-DS,5-N,2-ALS,1-AD (Box-folder 155:009)
- PERSONNEL--L.L. POND, MRS. RENNIE POOLE, LOIS PROCTER, EMERSON PRYOR, MRS. ADDIE RANGELEY, MRS. J.W. REMINES, ELDRIDGE REYNOLDS BY LOIS PROCTOR, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., N.D., 6-ANS,6-D,5-DS,14-tLS,5-N,9-TL,1-AN,1-NEWS,2-ALS (Box-folder 155:010)
- PERSONNEL--HARRY RICHMOND, CHRISTINE ROANE, B.A. ROBBINS, MRS. MARTHA ROLLINGS, E. PRESTON RUTTER, ELIZABETH RYAN, MRS. HIGH SCATES, MRS. LESLEY SCHISSELL, ROGER SCHMIDT BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: HARRY RICHMOND, ET AL., N.D., 27-TL,8-TLS,9-D,6-DS,2-AN,1-c.d.,2-N,1-ALS (Box-folder 155:011)
- PERSONNEL--RODNEY SEAGREAM, IRENE SEAHOLTZ, ELIZABETH SETTLE, MRS. E.E. SHANNON, MARY SHELTON, ESTEN SHOMO, CHARLES SMITH, MRS. WILLIAM SMITH, SAMUEL SNEED, KATHERINE SPENCER, MRS. W.B. SPONG, ROBERT STITH, JULIA STONE, MRS. W. STREET BY ROD SEAGREAM, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., N.D., 13-DS,12-TLS,12-D,15-TL,2-ANS,3-N,1-TLS,1-ALS (Box-folder 155:012)
- PERSONNEL--FRANKLIN STROUGH BY FRANKLIN STROUGH, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1966-1967, 10-TLS,7-D,8-TL,44-N, 2-PHOTO, 2-DS (Box-folder 156:001)
- MRS. J.J. SWECKER, MARY SWINBURNE, MRS. WILLIAM TAYLOR, MRS. FLOYD THOMAS, LIONAL ADRON TODD, MARY TUCKER BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: REBA PRICE, ET AL, N.D., 13-TL,11-TLS,2-AN,6-ALS,10-N,2-c.d.,7-D,10-DS,1-AD (Box-folder 156:002)
- PERSONNEL--ELOISE TUTTLE, THRIFT TYSON, JR., JOAN TIDWELL, PATRICIA UNDERWOOD, MRS. CHARLES VANCE, ALICE VAUGHAN, NANCY VENABLE BY LOUISE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., N.D., 6-N,1-NS,13-D,19-TL,19-TLS,10-DS,1-ANS,1-ALS (Box-folder 156:003)
- PERSONNEL--ELIZABETH VICK, JEAN WALDROP, MRS. B. HARRISON WALKER, MRS. RIPLEY WALKER, HOWARD WEIL, CHARLES WELLS, JR., ROBERT WELLS, JR., N.D., 6-DS,9-D,1-AN,3-TLS,6-TL (Box-folder 156:004)
- w.W. WENDT BY TAYLOR COPPING, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., N.D., 6-ANS,2-NS,2-NEWS,49-TL,18-D,4-N,17-TLS,6-ALS,4-c.d.s. (Box-folder 156:005)
  1-AD
- PERSONNEL--HOWARD WILLIAMS, JR., MRS. W. WARREN WILLIAMS, DAVID WILSON,CHARLES WOOD, MRS. JEAN WOOD, BERNARD WOODAHL, MRS. WRIGHT, CATHARINE ZAHAROV, MRS. BERYL ZEHMER, GEORGE ZEIGLER, III, N.D., 22-D,9-DS,19-TL,16-TLs,1-c.d.s.,10-N,1-ALS,1-ANS (Box-folder 156:006)
- PERSONNEL--MARY ELEANOR YANCEY BY MRS. YANCEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MR. BARRIE, ET AL., 1952, 14-D,58-TL,20-TLS,4-N, 1-DS (Box-folder 156:007)
- PERSONNEL PRACTICES QUESTIONNARIE, N.D., 27-DS,2-D (Box-folder 156:008)
- SELECTION COMMITTEE MATERIALS--ON EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR OF RICHMOND AREA TB ASSOCIAION BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: FRANK HARADER, ET AL., N.D., 34-TL,7-TLS,11-D,1-ALs,1-PHOTO,1-ANS,1-N (Box-folder 156:009)
- ASSOCIATIONS WITH FULL-TIME PERSON OTHER THAN EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR, N.D., 16-DS,1-AN,2-D (Box-folder 156:010)
- PERSONNEL PRACTICES BY VTRDA, N.D., 1-D (Box-folder 157:001)
- PERSONNEL PRACTICES BY VTRDA, N.D., 6-D (Box-folder 157:002)
- PERSONNEL PRACTICES AND POLICIES--VTA BY LESLIE FOSTER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: EXECUTIVE SECRETARIES, ET AL., -1949, 4-pam, 3-N, 19-D, 2-TLS, 1-TL (Box-folder 157:003)
  \
- PERSONNEL AND OFFICE ADMINISTRATION COMMITTEE BY VLA, ET AL., 1975-1976, 3-D (Box-folder 157:004)
- PERSONNEL AND OFFICE ADMINISTRATION COMMITTEE BY CHARLES E. DRINKARD, W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MEMBERS OF PERSONNEL AND OFFICE COMMITTEE, ET AL., 1969-1970, 14-D, 2-N, 5-TLS, 1-TL (Box-folder 157:005)
- PERSONNEL PRACTICES--LOCAL BY LOUIS DREXLER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LESLIE FOSTER, ET AL., N.D., 1-TLS, 25-DS (Box-folder 157:006)
- PERSONNEL PRACTICES--LOCAL ASSOCATIONS BY ARCHIVIST, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: H.A. DONOVAN, ET AL., 1950, 39-D, 2-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 157:007)
- PERSONNEL BY JOSEPH MOORE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., N.D., 4-ALS,33-D,4-N,34-TLS,42-TL,26-DS,3-ANS,2-AN,1-photo (Box-folder 157:008)
  1-C.D.S.
- PIEDMONT SANITORIUM, ANNUAL REPORT, REHABILITATIVE PROGRAMS BY MAX MURRAY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1961-1963, 9-N, 6-TL, 3-TLS, 1-ANS, 4-D, 1-DS (Box-folder 157:009)
- PIEDMONT SANATORIUM, ANNUAL REPORT, REHABILITATIVE PROGRAMS BY FRED BROECKER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: DIANA BRAU, ET AL., 1963-1965, 4-N, 3-D, 4-TL, 1-AN, 1-TLS (Box-folder 157:010)
- PIEDMONT SANATORIUM, STANFORD ACHIEVEMENT TESTS TAKEN BY PATIENTS, APPTITUDE TESTS, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN HISTORY, REHABILITATION PROGRAMS BY FRANCES GALLAGHER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: COL. WILLIAM NALLE, ET AL., 1950, 24-D, 6-N, 1-ANS, 9-TL, 5-TLS, 4-ALS (Box-folder 158:001)
- PIEDMONT SANATORIUM, STANFORD ACHIEVEMENT TESTS TAKEN BY PATIENTS, APTITUDE TESTS, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN HISTORY, REHABILITATION PROGRAMS BY FRANCES GALLAGHER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ADELE EVANS, ET AL., 1950, 27-D, 7-N, 7-TL, 3-ALS, 2-TLS, 1-AN (Box-folder 158:002)
- PIEDMONT SANATORIUM, REHABILITATIVE PROGRAMS, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN HISTORY BY NANCY LUTZ, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: JOHN HARRELL, ET AL., 1951-1954, 1-AN,13-D,24-TL,14-TLS,3-N,1-DS,1-NS,3-ALS (Box-folder 158:003)
- PIEDMONT SANATORIUM, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN HISTORY BY ETUY HALL, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: HAROLD MCGEE, ET AL., 1954-1958, 9-TLS,8-TL,23-D,1-AD,2-NEWSCLIP,8-N,3-ALS (Box-folder 158:004)
- PIEDMONT SANATORIUM BY STATE HEALTH COMMISSIONER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CHARELS SCOTT, ET AL., 1958-1959, 9-TL, 8-N,8-D,3-TLS,1-AD,2-ADS,1-ALS,1-AN,1-DS (Box-folder 158:005)
- PIEDMONT CONFERENCE BY EDGAR CARROLL, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MARY ALLEN, ET AL., 1952-1959, 20-D,4-AD,24-TL,1-NEWSCLIP,3-N,2-ALS,2-TLS,1-ANS (Box-folder 158:006)
- PIEDMONT CONFERENCE, QUARANTINE LAW, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN PUBLIC HEALTH BY MADELINE BROWN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: FRED BROECHER, ET AL., 1959-1960, 8-N,12-D,5-AN,3-ALS,3-TLS,5-TL,1-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 158:007)
- PIEDMONT CONFERENCE BY RUTH HARRIS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1960-1966, 24-D,16-N,8-AD,16-TLS,13-TL,4-pam (Box-folder 158:008)
- PIEDMONT SANATORIUM, REPORTS, HISTORY OF PIEDMONT, PIEDMONT SANATORIUM BECOMES A MENTAL HOSPITAL BY ED GAHAN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1965-1967, 6-N,8-D, 4-TL, 1-TLS, 3-NEWSCLIPS (Box-folder 158:009)
- PIEDMONT SANATORIUM, ANNUAL REPORT, REHABILITATIVE PROGRAM BY ETHEL DODSON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: FRED BROECKER, ET AL., 1959-1961, 5-TLS, 5-D, 7-N, 1-TL (Box-folder 158:010)
- PILOT STUDY INTENSIVE X-RAY SURVEY COMMITTEE BY CATHERINE ZAHAROV, ET AL., 1960-1961, 2-N, 2-D, 2-AD (Box-folder 159:001)
- PIEDMONT SANATORIUM, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN HISTORY AND PUBLIC HEALTH, APTITUDE TESTS FOR PATIENTS, REHABILITATIVE PROGRAM BY HEALTH EDUCATION DIRECTOR, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CHARLES SCOTT, ET AL., 1950, 1-ALS9-photos, 4-TL, 3-TLS, 15-D (Box-folder 159:002)
  FASCINATING 1950 LETTER FROM PATIENT VIVAN RICKS
- PIEDMONT SANATORIUM, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN HISTORY AND PUBLIC HEALTH, APPTITUDE TESTS FOR PATIENTS BY FRANCES GALLAGHEN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: HENRY COUNTY TRAINING SCHOOL, ET AL., 1950, 34-D,1-TLS,3-DS,4-TL,1-AL,1-ALS,3-AN (Box-folder 159:003)
- PIEDMONT SANATORIUM, PLANS AND FUNDRAISING FOR PIEDMONT, PATIENT CARE AND LIFE AT SANATORIUM, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN PUBLIC HEALTH, BY ETHEL DODSON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: HAROLD MCGEE, ET AL., -1949, 34-TLS,36-TL,3-DS,4-ALS,13-NEWSCLIPS,12-D,9-AN,2-N,1-AD (Box-folder 159:004)
  PIEDMONT BEGAN AS AN EXPERIMENT BECAUSE OFFICIALS WERE UNCERTAIN HOW BLACKS WOULD REACT. EMPTY BEDS AT FIRST. COMMENT--SUPERINTENDENT ASTUTELY REMARKS EVERY TUBERCULOSIS BLACK IS MORE OR LESS A MENANCE TO THE WHITES WITH WHOM HE ASSOCIATES..
- PICKNEY, THOMAS, 1952-1953, 1-NEWSCLIP, 3-D (Box-folder 159:005)
- PINE CAMP HOSPITAL BY TIMES DISPATCH, ET AL., -1949, 4-NEWSCLIP, 2-AN, 3-TL,4-D, 2-DS, 2-TLS (Box-folder 159:006)
- PINE CAMP HOSPITAL, SANATORIUM CARE, 1956-1957, 4-D, 23-NEWSCLIP, 1-TL, 2-TLS (Box-folder 159:007)
- PLAN OF ACTION--EMPHYSEMA, 1968-1969, 3-D, 1-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 159:008)
- PLANNING COMMITTEE BY ALICE PORTER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CAROL BOOBERG, ET AL., 1980-1981, 11-D, 1-TLS, 1-N, 2-TL (Box-folder 159:009)
- PLANNING COMMITTEE BY VLA, 1978-1980, 10-D, 9-TL, 13-DS (Box-folder 159:010)
- PLANNING COMMITTEE BY VLA-VTS, 1977-1978, 8-D, 2-N, 1-map, 1-DS (Box-folder 159:011)
- PLANNING COMMITTEE BY VLA, 1975-1977, 5-D (Box-folder 159:012)
- PLANNING COMMITTEE BY VLA, 1974-1975, 7-D, 3-N (Box-folder 159:013)
- PLANNING COMMITTEE BY VTRDA STAFF, 1972-1974, 15-D, 3-N, 1-N, 2-TL (Box-folder 159:014)
- POLICY AND PROGRAM TRENDS COMMITTEE BY VTRDA, 1969-1971, 9-D, 2-N, 1-TLS, 3-TL, 5-DS (Box-folder 160:001)
- POLICY AND PROGRAM TRENDS COMMITTEE BY VTRDA STAFF, 1968-1969, 20-D, 1-DS, 3-N, 3-TL (Box-folder 160:002)
- POLICY AND PROGRAM TREND COMMITTEE BY VTRDA STAFF, 1967-1968, 16-D, 1-TL, 2-N, 1-AN, 1-TLS (Box-folder 160:003)
- POLICY AND PROGRAMS TRENDS COMMITTEE BY VTRDA, ET AL., 1966-1967, 6-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 160:004)
- POLICY AND PROGRAM TRENDS COMMITTEE BY VTA, 1963-1964, 4-D, 1-N, 2-DS, 2-TL (Box-folder 160:005)
- POLICY AND PROGRAM TREND COMMITTEE BY VTA, 1962-1963, 8-D, 3-N, 4-TL, 2-DS, 2-TLS (Box-folder 160:006)
- POLICY AND PROGRAM TRENDS COMMITTEE BY VTA, 1961-1962, 7-D, 9-N, 3-TL (Box-folder 160:007)
- POLICY AND PROGRAM TRENDS COMMITTEE BY VTA, 1960-1961, 24-D,9-N,1-map,2-TL,2-ALS,2-AD,1-DS,1-TLS (Box-folder 160:008)
- POLICY AND TRENDS COMMITTEE BY VTA, 1956-1960, 15-D, 4-N, 1-DS, 1-TL, 3-TLS (Box-folder 160:009)
- POLICY STATEMENTS BY VTA, 1956-1958, 7-D (Box-folder 161:001)
- POLICIES--VTA--HD AGREEMENTS BY VTA, -1949, 4-N, 3-D (Box-folder 161:002)
- POSTER PROJECT--ART AGAINST TUBERCULOSIS BY CATHARINE ZAHAROV, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1960-1962, 1-pam, 2-N, 2-NEWSCLIP, 1-photo, 6-D (Box-folder 161:003)
- PRESIDENTS--VTA BY LESLIE FOSTER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ROBERT BARRIE, ET AL., -1949, 5-AN,12-NEWSCLIP,6-N,2-AD,17-D,6-TLS,3-TL,1-ALS,4-photo (Box-folder 161:004)
- PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION COMMITTEE--VLA/RR EMERGENCY CARE SUBCOMMITTEE BY VLA, 1975-1976, 2-D (Box-folder 161:005)
- PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION COMMITTEE--VLA/RR HOME CARE SUBCOMMITTEE BY VLA, 1975-1976, 1-D (Box-folder 161:006)
- PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION COMMITTEE VLA/RR PROGRAM PLANNING--EVALUATION SUBCOMMITTEE BY VLA, 1975-1976, 1-N, 1-c.d., 1-TL, 1-D (Box-folder 161:007)
- VLA/RR PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION COMMITTEE REHABILITATION WORKSHOP PLANNING GROUP BY VLA, 1975-1976, 3-D (Box-folder 161:008)
- PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION COMMITTEE--VLA/RR BY VLA, 1975-1976, 7-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 161:009)
- PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION PROGRAM BY VLA, ET AL., 1975-1976, 28-D, 4-pam, 2-N, 1-TL, 1-AD (Box-folder 161:010)
- PROGRAM OF WORK BY VLA, 1977-1980, 6-D (Box-folder 161:011)
- PROGRAM COMMITTEE BY DUDLEY ROCHESTER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: DONALD BRUMMER, ET AL., 1980-1981, 6-D, 1-N, 1-TLS (Box-folder 161:012)
- PROGRAM COMMITTEE BY TAYLOR COPPING, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: VLA STAFF, ET AL., 1978-1980, 10-D, 3-N, 8-TL, 14-DS (Box-folder 161:013)
- PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY VLA, 1975-1976, 6-D (Box-folder 161:014)
- PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY VLA, 1974-1975, 11-D (Box-folder 161:015)
- PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY VLA, 1973-1974, 16-D, 2-N (Box-folder 162:001)
- PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY VTRDA, 1972-1973, 3-D, 2-N (Box-folder 162:002)
- PROGRAM COMMITTEE BY VTRDA, 1971-972, 7-D, 1-TLS (Box-folder 162:003)
- PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY VTRDA, 1970-1971, 9-D (Box-folder 162:004)
- PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY VTRDA, 1969-1970, 9-D, 2-TL, 3-DS (Box-folder 162:005)
- PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY VTRDA, 1968-1969, 12-D, 1-AD (Box-folder 162:006)
- PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY VTRDA, 1967-168, 11-D, 1-N (Box-folder 162:007)
- PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY E.S. RAY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: EUGENE HUGHES, ET AL., 1966-1967, 22-D, 1-TL, 1-DS (Box-folder 162:008)
- PRESIDENT'S ANTI-POVERTY PROGRAM BY CATHERINE ZAHAROV, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: HELEN OSTWALD, ET AL., 1965-1966, 1-D, 1-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 162:009)
- PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY WILLIAM KINSER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CHARLES GREENE, ET AL., 1965-1966, 7-D, 2-N, 1-DS, 1-TLS (Box-folder 162:010)
- PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY W.E. KINSER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: E.C. DRASH, ET AL., 1964-1965, 5-D, 1-AD, 3-N, 2-TL, 1-DS (Box-folder 162:011)
- PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY E.C. DRASH, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MRS. J. YORK WELBORN, ET AL., 1963-1964, 12-D, 2-DS, 1-TL (Box-folder 163:001)
- PROGRAM OF WORK AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY VTA STAFF, 1962-1963, 2-N, 7-D (Box-folder 163:002)
- PROGRAM OF WORK AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY VTA, 1961-1962, 4-N, 5-D, 1-AN, 1-AD (Box-folder 163:003)
- PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE BY COLONEL B.M. BECKHAM, W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MEMBERS VTA PROGRAM AND BUDGET COMMITTEE, ET AL., 1960-1961, 5-D, 2-N, 1-TL (Box-folder 163:004)
- PROGRAM COMMITTEE BY VTA, 1956-1960, 11-D, 3-N (Box-folder 163:005)
- PROGRAM EMPHASES BY VTRDA, 1972-1973, 6-D, 1-N (Box-folder 163:006)
- PROGRAM EPHASES BY VLA, 1973-1974, 11-D (Box-folder 163:007)
- PROGRAM AND OPERATIONS COMMITTEE BY BERNARD WOODAHL, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: WOODWARD SHERMAN, ET AL., 1953-1954, 2-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 164:001)
- PROGRAM PLANNING--COMMITTEE PROCEEDINGS BY VTA, 1951-1953, 5-D (Box-folder 164:002)
- PROGRAM PLANNING--COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE BY VTA, 1951-1952, 1-N, 2-D (Box-folder 164:003)
- PROGRAMS BY VTA, 1952-1953, 3-D, 1-pam (Box-folder 164:004)
- PROGRAM AND WORK AND BUDGET BY VTRDA, 1964-1968, 8-D (Box-folder 164:005)
- PROGRAM OF WORK AND BUDGET BY VTA, 1963-1964, 5-D (Box-folder 164:006)
- PROGRAM OF WORK AND BUDGET BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: COMMITTEE MEMBERS, ET AL., 1961-1962, 6-D, 1-AD, 1-TL, 1-N (Box-folder 164:007)
- PROGRAM OF WORK AND BUDGET BY VTA, 1960-1961, 18-D, 3-TL, 3-N, 1-DS (Box-folder 164:008)
- PROGRAM OF WORK AND BUDGET BY B.L. HUMMEL, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: MEMBERS OF VTA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1959-1960, 2-D, 1-N (Box-folder 164:009)
- PROGRAM OF WORK AND BUDGET SAMPLES BY NTA, 1951-1963, 16-D, 1-N, 1-TL, 1-AD (Box-folder 164:010)
- PROGRAM OF WORK, -1949, 26-D, 1-TL, 1-AN, 1-N (Box-folder 164:011)
- PROGRAM PLANNING CONFERENCE BY VLA, 1977-1981, 1-AD, 3-TL, 5-N, 1-TLS, 1-ANS, 15-D (Box-folder 164:012)